//TODO: variables: correct, incorrect, unanswered
var correct = 0;
var incorrect = 0;
var unanswered = 0;

var Trivia = [
    {question:"q0", answer:"a0"},
    {question:"q1", answer:"a1"},
    {question:"q2", answer:"a2"},
    {question:"q3", answer:"a3"},
    {question:"q4", answer:"a4"},
    {question:"q5", answer:"a5"},
    {question:"q6", answer:"a6"},
    {question:"q7", answer:"a7"},
    {question:"q8", answer:"a8"},
    {question:"q9", answer:"a9"},
]

function init(){

}

//TODO: display start button to start game. init ();
//TODO: when start button pressed reset variables.
//TODO: load first question. question has mutually exclusive answers
//TODO: start timer. Possibly display spinner.
//TODO: if answered within time show whether correct of not.
//TODO: if answer correct display correct answer, "Correct!", and increment correct variable
//TODO: if answer incorrect display correct answer, "Incorrect" and increment incorrect variable.
//TODO: if no answer within time show correct answer and "Out of time!"
//TODO: after last question display correct, incorrect, and unanswered. with "Start Over?" button
//TODO: "Start over?" button restarts the game. init();

$(document).ready(function() {
    console.log( "ready!" );
    //  $("#answer4").attr("class", "form-check visible");
    //  $("#temp").text(Trivia[1].question);
});